SUNGBIN KANG

253-561-3186 sungbin9353@gmail.com

2023 N 154th Ct. Shoreline, WA 98133

PROFILE

Student at Graduate Certificate in Software Design & Development(GCSDD) in University of Washington Bothell that is focused on Object-oriented programming, data structures and algorithms in Java/C++.

A year of experience in object-oriented programming(Java & Python); developing, testing and debugging code; designing interfaces; and administering systems and networks.

Three years of experience as a software test engineer; analyzing, executing, and validating test cases, participating in product requirements.

Quickly learn and master new technologies; collaborative and communicative in both team and self-directed settings.

EXPERIENCE

Software Test Engineer, Tech Mahindra USA Inc.

Redmond, WA — July 2017 - August 2019

- Executed test cases for functional, validation, end-to-end, and regression testing for a Web application.
- Analyzed applications and errors, escalated issues to developers, and verified fixes.
- Reported and tracked bugs replicated reported customer bugs, verify bug fixes and new functionalities, regression tested new releases, supported developers by examining logs and debug files
- Operated and utilized debugging systems and programs to track and grab logs and debug files
- Cooperated and participated in product requirements or voluntary joint meetings with software developers for concerns of software improvement, error regression, and defect prevention.
- Strong familiarity and intimacy on a variety of Android-based models of UI and UX requirements.
- Managed and coordinated team schedules and tasks to keep deadlines of multiple deadlines.
- Strong familiarity and intimacy on a variety of OEM's models of UI and UX requirements.
- Hands-on experience on Google Project Fi testing with Android and iOS-based UX Samsung, LG, HTC, Xiaomi, Nokia, Apple, Google, etc.

Software Test Engineer, Jnd Solutions

Bellevue, WA — August 2016 – July 2017

- Coordinate and execute various testing activities in order to verify and defects within Android software.
- Utilize various testing tools and equipment in order to collect desired data for log analysis: QXDM, QCAT, DM, ADB, and/or etc.
- Evaluate software defects using bug tracking tool and assist development team members in the implementation of resolution strategies
- · Generate test reports to ensure rock-solid software quality
- Communicate and cooperate with both QA & development team members to deliver effective technical testing solutions

Manager/Barista, Richmond Beach Café

Shoreline, WA — June 2013 – January 2016

- As a manager, I check all inventory, record, and re-order all necessary products. I
 communicate with local businesses for products and fresh ingredients for our café. I manage
 finances, record the budget. I make the decision on dividing the work hours for our baristas
 and continue to train them. Establishing relationships with customers is important to me and I
 want them to know that we will do our best not only to fulfill their orders but to give them the
 confidence to continue to keep coming back.
- As barista, our menu is diverse from all coffee related drinks to bubble teas and smoothies.
 The menu also includes assortments of food items from sandwiches to crepes and pastries. I have a solid memory to know what customers ordered and I am calm to not get flustered during our busy times. I have the wherewithal to instruct the other baristas on what to make so we can utilize our time and work together.

EDUCATION

University of Washington Bothell, Bothell WA

SEP 2020 - JUN 2021

Graduate Certificate in Software Development & Design

University of Washington, Seattle WA

DEC 2012 - JUN 2016

Bachelor of Arts in Mathematics

Minor in Applied Mathematics

Seattle Central College, Seattle WA

SEP 2019 - MAR 2020

CSC 110 Introduction to Computer Programming (PYTHON)

CSC 142 Computer Programming I (JAVA)

North Seattle College, Seattle WA

MAR 2020 - JUN 2020 CSC 143Computer Programming II (JAVA)

SKILLS

- General Programming Skills
- Software Design
- Software Debugging
- Software Documentation
- Software Testing
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork
- Java
- BlueJ
- Eclipse
- Python
- Microsoft Visual Studio Code
- Linux
- Github